## LUIZ FILIPE DOURADO GALIZA

Born in 1988, Brazilian, married. I got my first official job in 2009 as a Software Developer. Before this, I used to do some web pages as a hobby. I tried to be a Technical Sales professional once, but, even though it was a good experience, I decided to turn back to my real passion which is software development.

over my country, Brazil.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

### Developer

Pitang Consultoria e Sistemas SA Jan 2017 - Mar 2018 Using agile methodologies like Scrum and XP, I had the opportunity to participate in three projects with different teams.

The 3rd one was a web application with Angular 2, WCF and other technologies aiming to understand the impact of weather on clean power generation.

Angular 2+ | WCF | SQL Server | .Net 4.6 with C# | Castle Windsor (IoC) | AspNet MVC + WebAPI | Aspose | TFS | Scrum

The 2nd one was a system written in WPF aiming to control load forecasts.

WPF | VSTO | .Net 4.5 with C# | Castle Windsor (IoC) | Informix | TFS | Scrum

And the 1st one was an ASP.NET MVC system aiming to maintain official journal publications and to control the taking actions according to these publications.

I was invited by Vectra to return for a Sales position since I was

As a result, we got a great contract where I oversaw the installation

of CA Application Management in all IT Departments from all courts

able to bring some clients in my first period onto this company.

jQuery | AspNet MVC | SQL Server | .Net 4.6 with C# | Castle Windsor (IoC) | TFS | Scrum

### **Technical Sales** Specialist (APM)

Vectra Consultoria é Serviços Ltda. Feb 2014 - Jan 2017

## Developer

Instituto DS Mamirauá May 2013 - Jan 2014 Responsible for the entire development of an Amazon trees extraction control system.

I chose to use Knockout as frontend (plus Bootstrap) and .Net 4.5 plus C# as backend. The database was SQL Server.

### Developer

Vectra Consultoria e Serviços Ltda. Sep 2011 - May 2013 I was contracted to develop a Web-based NOC support system. When the first version was delivered - which I wrote in ASP.NET Web Forms + C# + jQuery + SQL Server - my supervisors asked to me to mount a development team and to write the development process for the company, so I did it based on agile methodologies like Scrum.

### Developer

Apply Solutions Ltda. Aug 2009 - Sep 2011 Doing part of a development team for a quotation system written in ASP.NET Web Forms, SQL Server, jQuery and Report Viewer, I was able, after a while, to become the leader of this team due to my interventions the

I also was responsible, as an outsourced professional, to create an architecture in Zend (PHP) for a CRM system to a company called

### **EDUCATION**

### Postgraduate in Software Engineering (2016 - 2018)

Software Engineering - UNIBRATEC, Recife, PE, Brazil.

I had to stop this program in the last course (Android) due to delays from the institution, since my trip to Australia was already marked.

## Systems Analysis and Development (2008 - 2011)

Análise e Desenvolvimento de Sistemas - UNIBRATEC, Recife, PE, Brazil.

#### INFO

#### Location

Brisbane, QLD, Australia

#### Contact Phone 04 3514 7067

#### E-mail

Ifdgaliza@outlook.com S



#### LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/lfdgaliza

### Visa Type Student

# **SKILLS**

- C#, .Net standard and Core
- Angular 2+ and TS
- AWS
- JS, CSS, HTML and jQuery
- MVC and Web Forms
- WPF
- Git and SVN
- Agile Methodologies like Scrum
- TFS
- SQL Server
- MongoDB

### LANGUAGE

- Brazilian Portuguese (Native)
- English (Second Language) > Work in Progress

Speaking Listening Writing Reading